Yode Wang

UX Designer



+886 911 027827



https://yode0419.github.io/portfolio



Profile

I am an entry-level designer, a challenger in the field of UX design, with a background in civil structural engineering. Despite the different fields, I possess core capabilities required in this area: communication, coordination, design thinking, and problem-solving. Drawing, 3D modeling, presenting ideas, and considering feasibility are my specialties.

During my journey of self-study for this career transition, I have completed the Google UX Design course, accumulated UX portfolio projects, and built up my personal website. I am excited to bring my passion to UX, web and product design, aiming to provide users with enhanced experiences.

Experiences

2023.06 - 2023.08 Google UX Design Professional Certificate

Learning UX / Portfolio / Web Development

Structural Engineer 2016.09 - 2023.06

> **TYLIN Construction Consultant** Structural Design / Bridge Design / Project Management

- · Taoyuan Metro Green Line
- · Kaohsiung Metro Red Line
- · Taoyuan Airport Terminal 3
- · Hualien-Taitung Railway Dual-Track Project

Working Holiday in Australia 2019.13 - 2020.12

Perth / Melbourne

- · Crazy Sales Warehouse
- · The Pamphleteers Mail Delivery
- · Treviso Farm Grape Worker

Education

2013.09 - 2015.09 **National Taiwan University**

Master's Degree in Civil Engineering, Structural Division

National Taiwan University 2009.09 - 2013.09

AutoCAD

Bachelor's Degree in Civil Engineering

Skills

Front-End **Graphic Design 3D Modeling** Office Languages Development Word English Figma Blender HTML Photoshop SketchUp (Intermediate Level) PowerPoint CSS Illustrator Excel French **Engineering** JavaScript Procreate **VBA** (Beginner Level) Drawing Bootstrap